Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Development, Records SC0319
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of Development, records
1949-2013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Office of Development
SC0319
13.25 Linear Feet
Records of the Development Office pertain to fundraising efforts, particularly the PACE campaign of the 1960s (Plan of Action for a Challenging Era), The Campaign for Stanford, 1970s, and the Centennial Campaign. Included are correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, proposals, notes, statistics, and some clippings and articles.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Records in this collection include correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, proposals, notes, statistics, and some clippings and articles. They were received in several accessions, each of which has been listed separately. Records in accession 1984-069 pertain to the PACE Program (Plan for a Challenging Era) and include primarily announcements, summaries, publications, and clippings. Of note is an LP record with remarks by President Sterling, 1961, and Kenneth Cuthbertson, VP for Finance, 1963; and a parody publication consisting of photographs staged in the architectural model of the university. Records in accession 1984-149 pertain to fundraising in general and include summaries and reports on gifts. Records in accession 1991-012 pertain largely to planning for The Campaign for Stanford (1970s), with some records pertaining to the previous program, PACE. Included are correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, proposals, notes, statistics, and some clippings and articles, 1964-1977. Some files pertain to consultants, including Robert L. Conway, chairman of John Price Jones Company. The Campaign Case Statement folders (1969-76 mostly 1969-72) include memoranda, interview transcripts, notes, outlines, drafts of statements, and transcripts of remarks, all pertaining to a final document “The Case for Stanford.”
Stanford University. Office of Development; Stanford University. Office of Development; Stanford University -- Finance
- PACE Campaign, 1961-1964; Accession ARCH-1984-069
  - PACE Announcements, April 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Library (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Articles 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Radio Astronomy 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - PACE Campaign Summary 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Alumni Attitudes, Involvement and Giving 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - PACE Conclusion 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Book: "The Case for Stanford" (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Book: "Handbook for Committee Members" (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Book: "Stanford and Business" (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Book: "The Edge of Greatness" (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Parody: "What is a University?" with photographs staged in architectural model of the University (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Original clippings [not to be used for photocopies] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Original clippings [not to be used for photocopies] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - LP Phonograph Record: "Stanford PACE Program, Here's How"
    - Side 1: A discussion of proven techniques for PACE volunteers (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Side 2: 1. Remarks by President J. E. Wallace Sterling at the announcement of the Stanford PACE Program on April 18, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Side 2: 2. A review of PACE progress, 1963, by Kenneth M. Cuthbertson, Vice President for Finance (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Publications and photographs, 1971-1978; Accession ARCH-1984-079
  - Publications and photographs 1971-78
- Gift Statistics and Stanford Cabinet Minutes, 1956-1971; Accession ARCH-1984-149
  - Gift statistics, 1949-71
    - Gifts to Stanford 1905–1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gift Program Summary 1949–1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gift Program Summary 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gift Program Summary 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gift Program Summary 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Gift Program Summary 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gift Program Summary 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Gift Program Summary 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Gift Program Reports, September 1955 – August 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Gift Program Memos 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Parents Committee and Personal Solicitation 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Gift Program Summary 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Gift Program Reports, September 1956 – August 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Gift Program Memos 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Development Program Summary 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Development Program Reports, September 1957 – August 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Development Program Memos 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Development Program Summary 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Development Program Reports, September 1958 – August 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Development Program Memos 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Development Program Summary 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Development Program Reports, September 1959 – August 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Development Program Memos 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Development Program Summary 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Development Program Summary 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Development Program Reports, September 1961 – August 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Development Program Memos 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Development Program Summary 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Development Program Memos 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Development Program Summary 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Development Program Reports, September 1963 – August 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Development Program Memos 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Gift Procurement Program Reports, September 1965 – August 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gift Procurement Program Memos 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Gift Procurement Program Reports, September 1965 – August 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gift Procurement Program Reports, September 1966 – August 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gift Procurement Program Memos 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Unrestricted Fund Balances 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Gift Procurement Program Reports, September 1967 – August 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gift Procurement Program Reports, September 1968 – August 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Gift Procurement Program Summary 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIALS:
    - Confidential donor lists, 1949-71 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Notebook containing confidential memos and notes, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Campaign for Stanford Files, Accession ARCH-1991-012
  - Files on Campaign for Stanford
    - Robert Conway, memos on fundraising issues, 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Robert Conway, correspondence, notes, and memos, 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Robert Conway, memos, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Robert Conway, memos, 1972-74 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Robert Conway, correspondence and memos, 1970-75 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Robert Conway, memos, 1972-77 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Publications, correspondence regarding, 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Publications, correspondence regarding, 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 1 of 6 [Assorted summaries] (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 2 of 6 [The Campaign for Stanford 1972-77] (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 3 of 6 [Summary of Information Joint Meeting Stanford Cabinet / Trustees' Ad Hoc Committee on Gift Program May 10, 1971] (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 4 of 6 [same as folder 11] (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 5 of 6 [remarks of Daryl H. Pearson to Trustees and Cabinet, Jan. 12, 1970] (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Confidential Reports, 6 of 6 [remarks of Daryl H. Pearson to various groups, 1967-70] (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Robert Roche, correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Kersting, Brown & Co., correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 1 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 2 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 3 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 4 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 5 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Gifts Program, 6 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Gift Statistics, 1 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Gift Statistics, 2 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Gift Statistics, 3 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gift Statistics, 4 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Gift Statistics, 5 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Gift Statistics, 6 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Gift Statistics, 7 of 7 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Board of Trustees, correspondence, agenda, reports, etc., 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Board of Trustees, memos and reports, 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Public Relations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Affiliates Program, memos and reports, 1966-67 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Affiliates Program, memos 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Affiliates Program, memos and reports, 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Financial Report 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, 1 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Foundations, 2 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Foundations, 3 of 3 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Names (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee, 1 of 5 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee, 2 of 5 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee, 3 of 5 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee, 4 of 5 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee, 5 of 5 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pre-Campaign documents, 1964-1971, 1 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pre-Campaign, 2 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Campaign, 3 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Pre-Campaign, 4 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Pre-Campaign, 5 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Pre-Campaign, 6 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Pre-Campaign, 7 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Pre-Campaign, 8 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Pre-Campaign, 9 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Pre-Campaign, 10 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Pre-Campaign, 11 of 11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Communication with Volunteers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Northern California Leadership (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Components, 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Campaign Components, 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Components, 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Campaigns - Other Schools, 1 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Campaigns - Other Schools, 2 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Campaigns - Other Schools, 3 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Campaigns - Other Schools, 4 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 1 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 2 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 3 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 4 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 5 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 6 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 7 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 8 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 9 of 9 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Executive Committee 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Executive Committee, 1972-1973, 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Executive Committee, 1972-1973, 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1973, 1 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1973, 2 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1973, 3 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1973, 4 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1976, 1 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1976, 2 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Executive Committee to 1976, 3 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Long Range Gift Forecast 1967-1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Long Range Gift Forecast 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Cabinet, agenda and other materials pertaining to, 1970-72 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Organization (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Summary, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Associates, 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Associates, 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Executive Board (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dollar Goal - Feasibility (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Volunteers (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Solicitation Assignments, 1 of 4 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Solicitation Assignments, 2 of 4 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Solicitation Assignments, 3 of 4 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Solicitation Assignments, 4 of 4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Top 20 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Dr. Sterling's Assignments, 1974-76, 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Dr. Sterling's Assignments, 1973-75, 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Major Gift Program - Recap (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - PACE Retreat (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - PACE Campaign Statistics (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - PACE Campaign Financial Information, 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - PACE Campaign Financial Information, 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Last Year of Campaign (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Revised Campaign Plan 1974, 1 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Revised Campaign Plan 1974, 2 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Revised Campaign Plan 1974, 3 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Name by Name list of Prospects 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Special Gifts/Inner Quad Plan, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Retreat 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - University Budget Adjustments, 1 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - University Budget Adjustments, 2 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - University Budget Adjustments, 3 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Cabinet / Ad Hoc Committee pre campaign 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Progress Reports 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - New University Library (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gift Announcements (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Campaign Organization, 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Campaign Organization, 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Nucleus Fund (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Comments on President Pitzer (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Background Data on Stanford's Financial Needs, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Training Seminars (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Reconstruction of History Corner (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Big Gifts to Other Universities, 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Big Gifts to Other Universities, 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Gift Projections (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Report to President Lyman (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Introduction (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Major Gifts (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Annual Fund (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Special Gifts / Inner Quad (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Foundations Plan (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised Plan, 1972 - Communications and Public Relations (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Comparisons with Other Universities (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Introduction (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Major Gifts (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Annual Fund (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Special Gifts / Inner Quad (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Corporations Plan (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Foundations Plan (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, Revised 1974 - Communications Strategy (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Campaign Status Report, August - December 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Campaign Status Report, January - December 1973 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Campaign Status Report, January - November 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Status Report, January - December 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Status Report, January - December 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Status Report, January - April 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pre-Campaign Financial Estimates 1971-1972, 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Pre-Campaign Financial Estimates 1971-1972, 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Gift Table, 1 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Gift Table, 2 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Gift Table, 3 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Gift Table, 4 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Post Campaign (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Major Gifts (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Historical Society (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - General Fund Raising Articles (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Development Office Organization Chart 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIALS
    - Gifts $100,000 and over, 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gifts $100,000 and over, 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Former Trustees (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Committee Member Solicitation (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Trustees, Volunteer Campaign Service, 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Trustees, Volunteer Campaign Service, 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Trustees, Cabinet Gift Statistics, 1 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Trustees, Cabinet Gift Statistics, 2 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Trustees, Cabinet Gift Statistics, 3 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Trustees, Financial Information, 1 of 5 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Trustees, Financial Information, 2 of 5 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Trustees, Financial Information, 3 of 5 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Trustees, Financial Information, 4 of 5 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Trustees, Financial Information, 5 of 5 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Trustees, Annual Fund Solicitation (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Name by Name list of Prospects 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Gift Projections (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Gift Table (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Pre-Campaign Financial Estimates 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - PACE Campaign Statistics, 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Stanford PACE Program: Here's How and Plan of Action, Accession ARCH-1999-064 (Box SC LP 1)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2007-025
  General note
  Two additional boxes not Development-One with memorabilia (athletic mostly)-Second box on Sigma Chi fraternity
  - Portwood Chron File May-Aug 1987 to Chron File March-August 1990 (Box 1)
  - Portwood Chron File Sept-Feb 1990-1991 to Chron File March-June 1994 (2) (Box 2)
  - Portwood Chron File March-June 1994 (3) to Chron File August-September 1996 (Box 3)
  - Portwood Chron File Oct-Nov 1996 to Chron File August 1999 (Box 4)
  - Portwood Chron File September 1999 to Chron File November 2000 (Box 5)
    - Campaign for Stanford 1972-1977 (Box 5)
    - Ad Hoc Committee (1969) (Box 5)
    - Major Gift Assignments 4/21/76 Complete (Box 5)
    - Conway Memo on Campaign Communications, January, 1973 (Box 5)
    - The Campaign for Stanford Conway Memo to Ken and Daryl "How Are We Doing? November 1, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Campaign for Stanford (Box 5)
    - Planning for C. F. S. (Box 5)
    - SG/IQ Our Piece of the Action (Box 5)
    - Donors to Green Library (Box 5)
    - Annual Fund Campaign 1970 (Box 5)
    - 1975 Donor Down Analysis (Box 5)
    - Alumni Survey 1968 (Box 5)
    - SAF General—1966-1967 (Box 5)
    - Annual Fund 5 Year Plan 1968 (Box 5)
    - Stanford Associates Board of Governors Agenda May 1965 (Box 5)
    - Stanford Associates—Report of Long Range Planning Committee—1964 (Box 5)
    - COFHE Study 1976 (Box 5)
    - Stanford—CFS (Box 5)
    - Pearson Presentation on History of Campaign (Box 5)
    - Campaign—(History, Analyses, etc (Box 5)
    - DHP remarks 1970 (Box 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Files
    - Burr Gibson Survey (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - L/G Fromm, M/M Alfred (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Freshman applicants (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Freshman applicants (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Transfer applicants 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Medallion Nomination (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Paid Student Callers 6/91 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Associates—BAK (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Facts (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Tier III Survey (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - August 16, 1991 Seattle Ewart Thomas (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Fall 1991—Spring 1992 Games & Seminars (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy Weekend—Seattle 2/1-2/3/91 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 1991 Spring Seminar (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Portland Major Gifts Council 3/4/91 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Portland Major Gifts Council Meeting March 13, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Reception Briggs 3/20/90 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - William C. Janss Dinner—Sun Valley March 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Jean Skinner Dinner Party April 29, ‘90 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Seattle Major Gifts Council Meeting April 30, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Seminars Spring 1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Jane Russell Party—June 1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Portland Major Gifts Council Meeting, June 18, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - 1990 Football Luncheons (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Fall 1990 University Seminars (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Boise Event—Cocktail Party John Fery—October 3, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Major Gifts Council Meeting—10/22/90 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Reception Honoring G. P. Shultz December 10, 1990—Portland (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Phoenix NCC (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Major Gifts Council Meeting February 1989—Seattle (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Seattle Major Gifts Council Mtg Briggs Dinner March 1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Seminars Spring 1989 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pigott Dinner May 1989—Seattle (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Seminars Fall 1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Football Luncheons Fall 1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Notre Dame Football Luncheon September 1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Football Pre-Game Luncheon September 1989—Portland (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Andy Geiger Luncheon Spokane—October 1989 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Volunteer Breakfast/Prospect Lunch Seattle—October 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Andy Geiger Lunch September 8, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Centennial Campaign Nucleus Fund (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Public Announcement (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Announcement Luncheon—2/10/87 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - SOAC-CC Meeting March 21, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Centennial 100 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Centennial Campaign Activity Report (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Solicitation of Deans Centennial Campaign (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Campaign Tier III Letter (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Campaign: Timetable (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Campaign—Trustee Approval (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Campaign: Trustee Solicitation Plan (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Campaign: Donor Relations (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Association (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Student Development (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Rosters (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Trustees (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Endowed Professorship (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Foundations and Corporations (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Monterey Major Gifts Committee (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tier N, I, II, III PKM comments (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Campaign: Centennial Kickoffs (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Campaign—Case Statement Distribution (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Centennial Campaign—Case Distribution (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Consider Rating (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Human Resources Sub-Committee (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Culture Subcommittee (Box 7, Folder 20)